{
  "title": "Cybersecurity - Hard Level",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the default port for HTTPS?",
      "options": [
        "80",
        "443",
        "21",
        "22"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Linux command 'ls -l' display?",
      "options": [
        "File name only",
        "File type and file name",
        "Detailed list information",
        "File path and file name"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the 'nmap' tool primarily used for?",
      "options": [
        "Password cracking",
        "Network scanning",
        "Data encryption",
        "System monitoring"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the process by which plaintext is converted into ciphertext?",
      "options": [
        "Decryption",
        "Encryption",
        "Hashing",
        "Salting"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of attack involves intercepting and possibly altering communication between two parties without their knowledge?",
      "options": [
        "DDoS attack",
        "Man-in-the-middle attack",
        "Brute force attack",
        "Phishing"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What tool is commonly used for forensic imaging?",
      "options": [
        "Nessus",
        "Metasploit",
        "Wireshark",
        "Ftk Imager"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary purpose of OSINT?",
      "options": [
        "Password cracking",
        "Gathering data from public sources",
        "Intrusion detection",
        "Firewall configuration"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cryptographic algorithm is not symmetric?",
      "options": [
        "AES",
        "DES",
        "3DES",
        "RSA"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the function of a packet sniffer?",
      "options": [
        "To monitor network traffic",
        "To crack passwords",
        "To block malicious websites",
        "To encrypt data packets"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of a 'rainbow table' in hacking?",
      "options": [
        "To perform DDoS attacks",
        "To crack hash functions",
        "To sniff network packets",
        "To scan networks"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
}